[{"answer": "You know, Stan's a very good friend, and he did the right thing.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "And if you were advising Charlie Sheen now, what would you do to try and perhaps rebuild the bridge that's crashed around him?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, he's certainly playing a power game, but he's playing it with people like Warner Brothers, CBS, Les Moonves, Chuck Laurie.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "He's almost playing the Hollywood power game in his own way, and doing it in a way no one's done before, isn't he?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, no, of course not.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "You wouldn't deny taking hits of cocaine?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I just felt -- I felt a heavy heart.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "What did you make of the whole interview in context?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, I think there is a problem because, number one, as Bob said earlier, it was spiraling out of control.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "And if that private life is not adversely affecting his professional working environment, and it didn't seem to be much, then what's the problem?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "You know, I try to -- I tend to just focus on the here and now.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "I mean, do you look at a guy and think his life's in danger?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "When we ask about that, though, he says no, no reasonable person would shoot peaceful protesters.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Does he take any personal responsibility for the deaths of his people right now?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Does he think he can just ride this out?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, to your question about whether it's anti- American or whether it's the people here themselves, it is the people in this region themselves.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "And if that is the case, is this good for America and the west, do you think?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Piers, I'm -- couldn't be better.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Harvey, how are you?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, I was executive producer, but I had a bit to do with it.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Does it get better in Hollywood than being the guy that produced \"the movie\"?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "No kneecap.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "What happens in there?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "First of all, \"Social Network\" is a fabulous movie.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "What's the business of turning around an Oscar campaign?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I have to win for me, and I didn't kill them.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "But how did you kill it?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I think losing the Golden Globe for best picture for me, feeling that that was something that we could win was the absolute thing that instead of making me quit like a lot of people said, absolutely motivated me the complete opposite way.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "What was the key thing that you felt you had to do to get this film back on its tracks?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "There's only one thing to really do.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What are the key things you had to change?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "It's important to get it -- a movie connected to an audience, and it's important in an Oscar campaign.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "How important is it to get your front people out there selling that movie?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I was elated.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "ORGAN: When you heard the words \"best movie , 'The King's Speech',\" what did you feel?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "It's fantastic.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "One of the greatest moments of your life?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I worked with Charlie Sheen.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "What did you make -- what do you make of the Charlie Sheen story from a position of being a top producer in Hollywood?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "ORGAN: You think so?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I'd hire Charlie Sheen to do \"Scary Movie 4, 5, 6, 7.\"", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Would you hire Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I don't make TV series, so thank god.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Would you put him in a series maybe or no?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I have about -- probably 15 or 20 at home.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "How many Oscars have you got at home?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "You've got your work cut out there.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Well, I own a book called \"Mila 18\".", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "If you could make the ultimate movie for people dead or alive, you know, director, producer, leading man, leading lady, who would it be?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Probably producing it would be Hal Wallace and there's actually somebody alive who is young -- a young man at 87 years old, his name is Walter Mirsh.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "And who would produce it?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I think Katherine Hepburn could play the leading lady.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Best actor and actress you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Both Hepburns could play that.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "And the man?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "The simple answer is if you don't tell the story from both sides, you will never understand everything we're watching in Libya, Egypt, you know, et cetera.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "What's the simple answer?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Was that your intention, was it designed to inspire people more than anything else?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "By the time I was 18, yes.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "And she got -- she married four times and I think you moved how -- 17 times in 12 years?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "The sexual abuse, listen, when you're -- when you're 10 years old and you try to tell your parents, first of all the -- the -- the perpetrator says, you know, no one will believe you.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "But the sexual abuse?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "She said it's pretty personal.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "So what does she make of it?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "No, it wasn't that.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "But did -- did part of you think I should talk about this before other people do as your star rises?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Not -- not -- not with the abuse stuff.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Was that at the back of our mind as well?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "ROWN: Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "I mean, were you aware that what he was doing was wrong?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Embarrassment.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Why was that?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Well, I've moved on.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Well what are your thoughts to the man that abused you?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Yes, a little bit yes.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Strange feeling, isn't it?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "It was -- well, obviously you read the book --", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "And how bad was that?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, we'd be kind of banging on each other.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "He punching you?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Brilliant.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "And the judge, I think, is very smart, isn't he?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Well, it was Judge Zolf (ph) from Salem.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Tell me again what he does?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "He -- we were out about three weeks ago, went to breakfast and he said -- he looked me right in the eye and he said you know, I just want to say I'm sorry.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "Do you think he regrets what he did?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "Yes, Yes.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "But I can see in you now that that makes you emotional, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Is he proud of you now, do you think?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "Yes, mom's right next to Aryana (ph) absolutely.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "Was your mom there as well?", "qSentId": 788}, {"answer": "I wish it did.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "Does it have your head on it?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "It's been a very emotional 20 minutes, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "It meant nothing.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 828, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 827}, {"answer": "You know what I'm asking you.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "For what?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 854, "question": "Could you be tempted to run for president?", "qSentId": 853}, {"answer": "Well, I'm hopeful because people are obviously seeking freedom and democracy.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 862, "question": "What do -- what do you make of what's happening in the Middle East in the context of America?", "qSentId": 861}, {"answer": "Well, I think every -- every situation, you have to take it on its own merits.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "When you see what's going on in the Middle East, where it's happening in an evolutionary way, through the grass roots or the people themselves, isn't it a better way for America to go in the future?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "That's it.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 889, "question": "That's it?", "qSentId": 888}, {"answer": "OK, whatever.", "docId": "110301pmt", "aSentId": 892, "question": "How about that?", "qSentId": 891}]